## **SARAH TRAN**

408 759-0705 • contactsarahtran@qmail.com • linkedin.com/in/transarah/ • Los Angeles, CA

### Summary

Endlessly curious tech sales professional with 8+ years of experience selling to emerging - large enterprise markets. I am extending my skill set onto the product space via hands on software development in a variety of projects from MEN, MERN, to Django full-stack applications. I aspire to bridge the gap between my business acumen and development skills to bring meaningful products to life.

#### Education

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive 08/2023

San Jose State University

Sociology & Global Leadership & Innovation

06/2015

# Experience

Salesforce -Heroku

### Account Executive - Sr. Strategic

01/2018 - 04/2023

Mentored 3 new representatives who all ramped to 1st, 2nd, and 3rd achievement status' w/in a team of 8

Achieved 145% to quota and accepted to Salesforce's Global AE Excellence Academy which is reserved for the top 10% of AE's worldwide for consistent
achievement and leadership recognition

#### Account Executive - Growth Markets

Managed 300+ accounts of existing Heroku customers and responsible for lead generation in the mid-market and large enterprise space; \$23m book of business

- Awarded team MVP for achieving 112% to quota and closing the largest deal of the platform org. at \$1.7m
- Led monthly growth training programs which taught AE's how to hunt and grow their Heroku book of business resulting in a growth of \$20m in ACV across CORE products

#### Account Executive - Emerging Markets

Managed 200+ accounts of existing Heroku customers and responsible for lead generation in the emerging and SMB markets; \$18m book of business

- · Achieved 104% to quota year over year and recognized as 'Rookie of the Year'
- · Managed and grew the emerging business +20% YOY

Caspio Inc

Account Executive 04/2017 - 01/2018

Full cycle PaaS sales exec. for North American territory bringing in 12+ new accounts monthly

- Developed new qualification method for acct execs which early results show a higher 2nd call qualifying rate
- · Created an ESL communication best practices guide for EU and APAC sales teams

Google

#### Outbound Sales Development Rep

12/2015 - 04/2017

G Suite & Google Cloud Platform Outbound Sales Development Rep

- Generated 3M+ in pipeline, 1.5M+ in nurtured opportunities, 150K in closed deals Lead Q1-Q3 pipeline gen
- Lead 4 projects related to new go to market strategies, communication development, and pipeline management
- Reworked onboarding process for new hires and trained new sales representatives on best practices on job

#### **Projects**

MENS-Stack

### https://github.com/supersarahhh/dep-

Inspired by my Vietnamese roots. Dep is an MEN-stack application with full CRUD capabilities and serves as a database of Vietnamese owned e-commerce businesses.

MERN-Stack

### https://github.com/supersarahhh/flock

Flock is an event search application; built utilizing Ticketmaster's discovery API and Spotify player embed tools. Made for not only finding events, but for connecting with other users of similar interests.

Diango Full-Stack

### https://github.com/supersarahhh/Meridio-Full-Stack-App

Merido is my first group development project built with Django and a Postgres SQL backend. Designed for eco-friendly purchasing in mind, the application is aims to shrink carbon footprints and encourage community relationship building.

Powered by CY Enhancy